FLY to the future with wings flapping and Spotlight shining
We will now begin the final round of judging.
Thank you very much.
There are eight members.
The first one is...
Announcement applause.
I think I'm as good as anyone at practicing dance and singing.
Yes, I know.
I don't really understand the lyrics if I give it a 3
Oh,
I had to look it up and memorize the lyrics because I've been wanting to close my eyes for a long time now, and it's still like a kid's day.
Thoughts are the best
Come with me, New World
The second one.
Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily.
Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily, Lily
Applause
I joined this group because I wanted to change myself that I couldn't take a step forward.
I usually work, so I managed to take time out of my morning and evening hours to practice every day.
Lily's VoiceI've been taking time out of my morning and evening hours to practice every day.
Mikibitismonlight I feel like I definitely have color on this tip.
To the game of three table of contents
I'd never give up on anything, but every time I'd get to a certain point, I'd think, I can't compete with that.
And the fourth person
Suzuna Suzuna
I wasn't very confident in that voice.
If I get this survival of myself
I would get up to be what I want to be.
I wondered if I could become a version
I'm going to give it a try.
My voice, it's indie.
The band is practicing
Practicing 好可愛好可愛Who's up for the next challenge? Who's up for the challenge? Who's up for the challenge?
Who's up for the challenge?
Who will challenge me?
Who will challenge?
Who will challenge? Who's up for the challenge? Yes hello everyone and welcome to my first ever Instagram Live.
Did you have a good time?
Thank you.
Great.
Last take.
Let's go.
Six.
Six. Six.
Six. Six. Six.
Haruho Haruho
It seems like only yesterday that I actually had an audition or something, Haruho.
I had given up on auditioning, but I succeeded and now I'm doing my best to support you.
Thank you very much.
I think I can't sing because of my throat... and my body's safety.
I have a reputation for not being able to sing.
I want to sing, but I can't.
That's stress and anxiety, and I'm moving on to the next stage.
Nanky, since the end, I've been up on various stages.
I've been up on stage over a thousand times.
I want to be an idol who can change someone's life in 3 times.
Let's go together, newbie, in this wide world.
I want to sing with you, I want to sing with you, I want to sing with you, Liner
We can go anywhere you want
I'd like to announce the last one.
The eighth one is นี่มันอะไร์เปล่านี่มันออนไร์เปล่านี่มันออนไร์เปล่าน
นี่่
นี่ Real Real Real Real
Real Real
REAL
Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real
Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real Real
real
Real
I'm good at dancing.
But I couldn't remember the choreography at all.
I still have a lot of growing up to do.
I want to work harder. I'm so happy to be here now, and believe me, I want to work harder.
These are the 8 members who will be working as Fu-Fu.
I look forward to working with you.
Hello?
There it is.
Coming soon.
Eight members.
That's great.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Okay, bye-bye, thank you, thank you, thank you... thank you... for being a member of this group.
Uhhh...
Oh...
Excuse me.
Mom, did you get it? Phone.
She picked up.
She said congratulations.He said congratulations.
This training camp was amazing.
I cried at home.
I was kind of sick.
He was really worried about me.
Whether I got in or not.
He told me that it wasn't the end of the world.
He told me to go out there and do my best.
But I don't know...
Since I was very young.
I've taken lessons and auditions before.
I've always reported that I didn't make it, so...